Kuusamo
Helsinki
A smoky, foggy city
People don't know even their neighbour
Everyone's in a hurry
Only a few in here smile
Invisible strings are pulling and ripping apart marionettes
Who are bouncing around like prey fish
Everyone's in a hurry to nowhere
Kuusamo
I can hear Kuusamo calling me
I see a sturdy forest
And a blue-shaded hill
Kuusamo
I can hear Kuusamo calling me
Only there will I find peace
Helsinki has no residents anymore
Only lonely people, which there are many
Too many
I wouldn't want to be one of them
I want to be free and breathe the smell of sprig
Here I'm like a prisoner
I shall go to Kuusamo
Kuusamo
I can hear Kuusamo calling me
I see a sturdy forest
And a blue-shaded hill
Kuusamo
I can hear Kuusamo calling me
Only there
will I find peace
Far away
Joy is far away
I lost my peace of mind
But perhaps I'll get it back
The only
Place without hate
Wilderness
Share it with me