Hey friend, wipe off your tears of pain,
you're making them in vain,
I'm carrying my mandolin on top of my backpack.
Yeah, I remember you;
I wrote your address on it too,
I wrote your address on it too.
This journey of the travelin' Mandolin Man
is so full of life that I can
sometimes forget how there's someone waiting for me.
But I remember you
I wrote your name on the mandolin too,
I wrote your name on the mandolin too.
I'll toast for you somewhere,
I'll bring you something there.
I could of course fill my bottle with mountain air,
or with Atlantic water's flair
I'll bring them to you when I get back there,
I'll bring them to you when I get back there.
Hey stranger listen to this song
as the wine warms us daylong!
I wrote these stanzas on the back of my mandolin,
soon you'll know too
the girl who I left when away I flew,
the girl who I left when away I flew.
I'll toast for you somewhere,
I'll bring you something there.
I could of course fill my bottle with mountain air,
or with Atlantic water's flair
I'll bring them to you when I get back there,
I'll bring them to you when I get back there.
Hey friend, wipe off your tears of pain,
you're making them in vain,
I'm carrying my mandolin on top of my backpack.
Yeah, I remember you;
I wrote your address on it too,
I wrote your address on it too.