Once the promise of heart was given
Promise of heart between us two
No power or force
That can take it away
Do you remember that promise of heart
Promise of heart that binds us together
Promise of heart forever
No place or time
Can change its magic
Do you remember that promise of heart
Promise of heart is a secret
Only for two people
Others do not need to know
Others do not need to bear it
Do you remember that promise of heart
Promise of heart never to be forgotten
Do you remember when we once stood
On a winter night under the stars
And with a quick kiss
Sealed the promise of heart
Promise of heart is a secret
Only for two people
Others do not need to know
Others do not need to bear it
Do you remember that promise of heart