He sits at the beach bar
Drinks cold beer
He watches the ships
That sail by so slowly
Oh what a wonderful evening
Anything can happen
He meets many friends
But wishes he would meet someone
Who would be more than that
She gets up from the bathtub
Wraps her long hair in a towel
She paints her nails
Goes out into the warm air
Oh what a wonderful evening
Anything can happen
She meets many friends
But wishes she would meet someone
Who would be more than that
Oh what a wonderful evening
Anything can happen
He meets many friends
But wishes he would meet someone
Who would be more than that
Later on the beach boulevard
These two meet each other
They watch the ships for a while
Then go
Their separate ways again
Oh what a wonderful evening
Anything can happen
He meets many friends
But wishes he would meet someone
Who would be more than that
Oh what a wonderful evening
Anything can happen