I sing my last song and leave
And I won't ever come back to you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)
Into the forest I vanish and dig my grave
Maybe I'll shed a tear for you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)
I wake up in the city center, the air is cool, I have to leave
They don't understand, darkness falls before you wake up
I'm a ghost, I'm a phantom, you won't see me again
But it's not your fault, I don't want to see anyone anymore
I've lost my significance in this circus
Now the curtain falls, I stop this performance
This isn't me, the one I lost, I'm searching now
And even though I won't come back, you were special to me
I sing my last song and leave
And I won't ever come back to you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)
Into the forest I vanish and dig my grave
Maybe I'll shed a tear for you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)
Birds follow me in the city, they want to peck at me
They're like a horror story, I dare not move
When I'm losing it, the sky is always dark with birds
When I'm not, they're not there, the birds are just an illusion
I have black superstar sneakers, black Rikus on my feet
I'm a mixer of chaos, I'm neither a bird nor a fish
I've crossed the border, dear, I won't come back anymore
I don't want to make money, I want everything to burn
I sing my last song and leave
And I won't ever come back to you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)
Into the forest I vanish and dig my grave
Maybe I'll shed a tear for you
I disappear without a trace (Haahh)