A little boy can not trust women,
they produce a big longing in the little heart.
But to stare at the window, the little boy perhaps gets to do in evening,
therefrom the princess of my dream looks out.
From behind the pane, from behind the pane,
from behind the pane, my girl just looks.
She is the most beautiful of women that I know,
I endure the small breasts on my princess.
The hat is immaculate, and so is the body posture.
From behind the pane, my girl just looks.
Oh, Glendora, oh Glendora,
oh Glendora, how I worship you.
Once again I am at the window one evening,
now a guy enrobed another princess in a gown.
He enrobed the head and he enrobed the rest,
replacing it with a decorated doll.
Behind the pane, someone else took my girl.
Behind the pane, behind the pane,
behind the pane, someone else took my girl.
Someone else took her, someone else took her,
someone else took her, someone else took her,
someone else took her...