You were my only friend
When we spent those summers together
You were my cat woman
You didn't want to be like the others
The stars and the moon weren't enough for you
You were so different
I have missed you Kyllikki
When the wind of fate rocks the bark ship
You were posing in the men's magazine
And I'm insulted as a drunkard in the upright bar
You secretly escaped to the city
You no longer replied to my letters
You probably found someone else
I somehow ended up here too
And from the newspapers, I read everything about you
I wouldn't let you leave my side anymore
I have missed you Kyllikki
When the wind of fate rocks the bark ship
You were posing in the men's magazine
And I'm insulted as a drunkard in the upright bar
You were my only friend
When we spent those summers together
I wouldn't let you leave my side anymore
I have missed you Kyllikki
When the wind of fate rocks the bark ship
You were posing in the men's magazine
And I'm insulted as a drunkard in the upright bar
I have missed you Kyllikki
When the wind of fate rocks the bark ship
You were posing in the men's magazine
And I'm insulted as a drunkard in the upright bar